人人影视
YYeTs.com
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译： 暴龙蛋      圈圈      阿髻
翻译： 苏小黛      Kiko      DustD
时间轴： 浓子   萌    校对： 苏小黛
后期： 孤帆    总监： 米小勒   胖兔纯
塞勒姆
第一季  第十集
《塞勒姆》前情提要
Previously on "Salem"...
父亲
Father?
把她关起来
Take her to the cage.
柯顿  柯顿
Cotton! Cotton!
你好  父亲
Hello, father.
你依然会被卖掉  如果妓女还要你
You'll be sold still, if the whores will have you.
我哪都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
对不起
I'm sorry.
带她到马匹所能及的最远之处
Take her as far as your steeds will travel.
告诉我们  梅西  告诉我们你看到了什么
Tell us, Mercy. Tell us what you saw.
她将一个蜘蛛捧在肩头
She held a spider to her neck.
她好像在喂它
She seemed to feed it.
你
You.
我在此以
I hereby arrest you...
涉嫌巫术的罪名逮捕你
on the charge of witchcraft.
守卫
Guards.
你的怒火中烧
Your wrath burns like fire.
你视我如无物
You look upon me as worthy of nothing.
你纯净的目光中
You are of purer eyes
容不下我的存在
than to bear to have me in your sight.
在你眼中  我比万恶的毒蛇
I am 10,000 times more abominable in your eyes
还要让人憎恶
than the most hateful, venomous serpent is in mine.
我的罪恶让我万劫不复
My wickedness makes me as heavy as lead,
如果你不再眷顾我  主啊
and if you should let me go, Lord,
我愿意堕入地狱
I will plunge into the bottomless pit,
我所有的正义不再能
and all my righteousness would have no more influence
支撑我逃出生天
to uphold me and keep me out of hell
就如螳臂焉能当车
than a spider's web would have to stop a falling rock.
还有什么话对你父亲说吗
Any last words for your father?
愿恶魔像你对我那样
May the devil be as kind and considerate to you
照顾你
as you were to me.
我想梅西了
I miss Mercy.
我们的梅西永远于我们同在
Our Mercy is always with us.
也许那家伙现在是梅西的仆人之一了
Perhaps that's one of her servants now,
照顾着我们  编织着命运的网
watching over us and weaving its web of destiny.
梅西
Mercy...
你躲不了的  这可是我家
You cannot hide from me in my own house.
你为什么那么做
Why did you do it?
你怎么能
How could you?
赶紧给我出来
Come out from there at once.
我是为了你啊
I did it for you.
为我
For me?
他是冲着你来的
He was coming for you.
如果我没所作为
If I hadn't done anything,
现在就是你在受难了
it would be you in the house of pain.
你应该感谢我
You should thank me.
也许吧
Perhaps.
但这由不得你做主
But it was not up to you.
*擂我战鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鸣震天*
*Witch drums*
*擂我战鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鸣震天*
*The witch drums*
*宁入地狱*
*Better pray for hell*
*不留人间*
*Not hallelujah*
找到你了
There you are.
我认识缇图芭甚至比你更久
I have known Tituba even longer than you have,
那时候她还是个孩子
ever since she was a small child.
她这一生经历了很多
With all that she has endured in her life,
如果说谁最可靠  那肯定是她
if there is anyone who can hold out, it is she.
如果
"If."
小小的一个词儿
Such a small word
却要承担我们所有人都无法承受的后果
with such immense consequence for all of us.
你必须信任她
You must trust her.
她会利用好机会的
She will use the opportunity.
机会
Opportunity?
折磨也算机会吗
You call torture an opportunity?
我说的机会  是把英克里斯的注意力
The opportunity to divert Increase's attention
向我们所希望的方向转移
to where we want it and away from where we do not.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我接受不了
I can't bear it,
一想到他会怎么折磨她
the thought of what he might do to her.
我不会坐视不理的
I won't stand for it.
你觉得怎么样
Do you like it?
"苦痛出真言"
"Truth through pain."
我觉得还挺合适的
I find it a fitting,
算是对塞勒姆的好人们最委婉的示意吧
almost poetic demonstration to the good people of Salem
这正是他们目前最需要做的
as to what is now expected of them. Hmm?
你想想  把这个
Imagine transforming
寻花问柳的地方
this house of woebegone pleasure
变成一间忏悔室
into a place of repentance.
我听说他们已经给它起名叫苦难屋了
I understand already they call it my house of pain.
你同意了吗
And you approve?
是的  是的  我同意
Oh, yes. Yes, indeed, I do.
让人们打心眼儿里记住这些苦痛
Oh, keeping the pains of hell foremost in one's mind
是最可靠...  不  不
is the surest... nay, nay, the...
是唯一能防止他们虚度年华的办法
the only road to prevent spending eternity there.
今天有什么我能帮你的吗
And how may I help you this fine day?
你关了一个我的人在这儿
You keep someone here that belongs to me.
我有充分的理由相信
Well, I have very good reason to believe
她属于恶魔
that she belongs to the devil himself.
胡说
Nonsense.
我从小就认识她了
I've known her since we were girls.
老实说  她不只是我的仆人
Truth be told, she is not just my servant.
她也是我的朋友
She is also my friend.
我在想
Well, I wonder, then,
也许正因为跟自己的女主人成为朋友
becoming befriended by...by one's mistress
才让她误入歧途的
is perhaps the reason that she went astray.
也许...
Perhaps...
也许不是她
Perhaps it is not she,
而是你  来这里会更加受益匪浅
but... but you who could most benefit from being here.
你好像忘记是在跟谁说话了  父亲
I think you forget to whom you are speaking, Father.
柯顿都能起床走动了啊  很好
Cotton up and about. Good.
不不  我知道这是玛丽·西布里
No, no. I know this is Mary Sibley,
我的朋友乔治的妻子
wife of my friend George,
就是在她的悉心照料下
under whose under tender care
乔治莫名其妙地形同枯槁了
he has mysteriously withered into an invalid.
您这话什么意思  先生
I resent your implications, sir.
我没什么意思  只是直说而已
I imply nothing. No, I say outright.
往好了说  你只是个软弱不负责任的女人
At best, I find you to be a weak and irresponsible woman.
往坏处想的话...
And at worst... well,
我们还是不要往坏处想了吧
let us not even consider the worst.
不不  我该对乔治
No, no. I shall take responsibility
还有那个奴隶  缇图芭负责
for George and for the slave,
至少目前如此
Tituba, for the time being.
与此同时  我建议你回家
Meantime, I suggest you get you home
回到西布里先生的七角尖阁里去吧
to Mr. Sibley's House of Seven Gables.
小说《七个尖角阁的老宅》
描写了一个家族前人作孽后人遭殃的故事
柯顿  我们去办事
Cotton, to business.
撕舌器
Tongue tearer.
这个是用来
This is for
让我们审讯的人开口讲出真话的
snipping the lies from the mouths of those we question.
碎骨器
Skull crusher.
夹乳钳
Breast ripper.
这些东西
Both of these are,
都简单粗暴  名如其物
well, quite aptly, if somewhat crudely, named.
父亲  我曾经把一个无辜的人逼死
Father, I once pressed an innocent man to death.
肯定有更好的方法
There must be a better way.
父亲  你得知道  囚犯为了
Father, you must know, a tortured prisoner
免受折磨  肯定会承认任何事的
will confess to anything to stop the pain...
任何事  不论真假
Anything... true or not!
对  确实如此
Yes, that is surely so.
但是如果你以为我会笨到
But you...you grossly mistake my faculties
相信一个刚被拷打之人
if you think me fool enough to accept as truth
因为痛苦而说出的一切
the first pained pourings that invariably come
那就太低估我的刑具了
from the tormented lips.
但是  真相显而易见...
But, sir, it is a self-evident truth...
没有真相是显而易见的
I take no truth to be self-evident,
可能今天这里发生的
save perhaps that whatever acts of horror
一切恐怖行为
take place here today
都是我不在期间你的松懈倦怠造成的
are due entirely to your laxity during my absence.
不要让他误导你
Do not let him mislead you,
不要妄想
and abandon all hope
他或者其他任何人来救你
of your deliverance by him or by any other agent.
现在你需要做的
Now, what you must do
就是思考...
is meditate...
你眼前的这些工具
on these instruments which you see before you.
你必须一心一意
You must set your mind
去追求那些
firmly in pursuit of the goals
你必须实现的目标
which you must achieve,
也就是你的生存和你的救赎
that of your survival and your salvation.
异端尖叉
The heretic's fork.
好
Yes.
让你时刻集中注意  保持警觉
To keep you attentive and alert during the process.
还有这个...
And this...
你肯定知道是什么吧
Well, this you surely recognize --
这是拇指夹
Thumbscrews.
我觉得这是最简单
I believe these to be the simplest,
最高效的刑讯工具了
and yet the most effective method of revealing the truth.
我们开始
And so let us begin.
你使用宗教法庭的
You employ the very tools of oppression
镇压工具...
perfected by the inquisition...
那些称我们为异教徒的人
...tools used against good puritans
用来对付善良清教徒的工具
by those who would call us heretics.
这叫以毒攻毒  孩子
Fire with fire, my boy.
她人呢  安去哪里了
Where is she? Where is Anne?
你的傻瓜女儿
Your foolish daughter
做了件非常危险的事
has done something exceedingly dangerous.
她戴了我的面具
She put my mask on.
那快点把她带回来啊
Well, bring her home this instant.
我做不到
I cannot.
每次只能有一个人用
Only one traveler may use it at a time,
鉴于她没有经验
and as she has no experience,
所以肯定不知道怎么才能利用面具回来
she will have no idea how to use it in order to get back.
现在这个面具只会成为对付我的证据
The only possible use for it now is as evidence against me.
可她去哪里了
But where has she gone?
去树林了
To the woods.
我会找到她的
I shall find her.
你有勇气去面对印第安人
You, man enough to face Indians...
面对野狼  面对你假装能控制的魔鬼吗
and wolves or the devils you pretend to command?
我也别无他法
There is no alternative.
那就想个办法
Find one,
我发誓...
for I swear by...
以你敬若神明的那个东西发誓
by whatever it is you hold holy,
如果今晚我们的女儿没在自己床上安睡
if our daughter is not asleep in her own bed this very night,
我一定会到处去说  直到你
my tongue will wag until you are tied to a stake
被绑上绞刑架为止
in the middle of the commons.
注意点  妻子
Take care, wife.
你这样只会害了自己
You shall only implicate yourself.
那我们就玉石俱焚吧
Then we will taste each other's ashes.
这是梦  只是个白日梦而已
This is a dream... nothing but a waking dream.
那个面具
The mask.
父亲的研究
My father's study.
这片树林
These woods.
只是个梦罢了
It's all but a dream.
此时此刻  我正躺在卧室的床上
At this moment, I lie upon my bed in my room...
就在家里
at home.
快醒醒
Wake up!
醒醒
我怎么来的不重要
It doesn't matter how I got here.
我得回到塞勒姆
I must get back to Salem.
东边
East.
这边走
This way.
你怎么知道她在树林里
What makes you think she's in the woods?
我了解自己的女儿
I-I know my daughter,
了解她的想法  也知道她有时根本不加思考
how she thinks and how at times she doesn't.
我知道你觉得我作为塞勒姆
I-I know you feel that I have somehow failed
秉持天赋人权的治安官
in my duties as... as magistrate
多少有些失职
to uphold the natural rights here in Salem
也明白你对我那些阴暗的揣测
And that you hold whatever dark suspicions you do about me.
但我不是为了自己
But I ask not for myself.
是为了安
For Anne.
走吧
Let's go.
谢谢你
Thank you.
等发现她还活着再谢我吧
You can thank me if we find her...alive.
自地狱中拯救吾等吧  天父
Save us from hell, Father?!
你现在所做的
Is that what you're doing
是在拯救吾等于地狱吗
saving us from hell?
已经太晚了
Well, too late.
塞勒姆就是地狱  我则身在其中
Salem is hell, and I am not out of it.
我是你创造之物
I am the creature you have made.
我无法成为你希望的样子
I cannot be who you will me to be,
但我又没有其他的志向
yet I lack the will to be anything else.
像是畸婴出世
Like that monstrous birth,
我还不如不出生的好
it were better had I never been born.
但我无法打破时间的沙漏
Though I cannot draw back the sands of time,
无法停止时间流逝
I can break the hourglass.
再见了  天父
Goodbye, Father.
我会在地狱安家  等待与你相见
I will make my home in hell and await you there.
太软弱了
Weak.
我连这微弱的烛光都无法熄灭
Too weak even to snuff this feeble candle.
你很厉害
Well, you're wonderful.
颇有本事
Quite remarkable.
你列出了村里起码半数人的名字
You've named at least half the people in the village.
当然了  他们都不是巫师
Of course, none of them are witches.
你如此迫切地供出他们  恰恰证明了这一点
The fact that you offer them up so eagerly attests to that.
但你已经进步不少了
But you made great progress.
我们就要拨开谎言的迷雾了
We are working our way through the lies.
要不了多久  那一刻就会到来
Very soon, we will come to that precise moment
当痛苦难以承受
when the agony will be so unendurable
即使谎言之王
that even a-a loyal servant
最忠实的仆人  也将背弃谎言
of the prince of lies can lie no longer.
这个工具
This tool...
它叫做涩梨子
it is called the choke pear,
我也听说过叫"痛苦之梨"
Although I have heard it called the pear of anguish.
它能伸进黑暗的穴洞之中
It is inserted into the darker cavities and then...
然后张开
...opened up,
洞中的东西
with the expectation
也会被撑开
that the subject, too, will open up.
现在  给我真正的名字
Now, tell me the real names.
在塞勒姆天上的父啊  你徒有其名
My father, who art in Salem, hollow be thy name.
你的国已毁
Thy kingdom's done,
你的旨意行在地上
Your will I shun,
已遭背离
on Earth...
如同行在你那天堂铸就的地狱之中
As in the hell you'd make of heaven.
魔鬼要来带我走了
The devil himself come to take me.
带我走吧  魔鬼
Take me, devil.
我本该将生命的每一刻当做最后一刻
I should have lived every hour on Earth as if it were my last.
现在就是最后一刻了
And now it is.
置之死地而后生
Out of death comes life.
我明白了  主  这才是你的本意
I see now, Lord, that is your true face.
你不会理解我做了什么
You cannot know what I have done
又侍奉了谁
or who I have served
除非你先知道原因
until you know why.
那么
So...
就告诉我
then tell me.
为什么
Why?
为了正义
For justice.
我不是巫师
I am not a witch.
也不是清教徒
I am not a puritan.
我是阿拉瓦克部落人
I am of the Arawak tribe...
或者曾经是
or I once was.
但当我闭上双眼
But I close my eyes,
我仍能看见那些翠绿的灌丛
And I can still see the green of my jungle
以及英国佬那些惨白的面孔
and the deadly white of the Englishmen's faces.
我以前从没见过那种肤色
I had never seen skin like that,
如此苍白  他们向我们走来时
so white when we see them walking towards us,
我们以为那是幽灵
We think they are ghosts.
奴隶
Slavers.
他们屠杀了我们大多数的男人
They slaughtered many of our men,
用铁链铐住剩下的
chained the rest,
然后对女人纵享其欢
and have their way with the women.
我还太小  对他们毫无用处
I am too young to be of use to them,
但妈妈和姐姐们就不同了
but my mother and sisters are not.
他们还强迫我去看
and they forced me to watch.
之后  挂着镣铐的我回头望去
Later, in chains, I look back,
他们将村里的棚屋付之一炬
and they're burning the huts of my village,
我看到树林之外
And I see two red eyes staring back at me,
有两只血红的眼睛盯着我
out of the trees.
接着它们开口对我说
And the red eyes speak to me,
"缇图芭  你是我的"
"Tituba, you are mine."
撒旦对我们说话时  总会用我们的母语
Satan speaks to each of us in our own native tongue.
现在  还要继续吗
And now shall we continue?
这里不久前有人来过
Someone came through here quite recently...
某些迷失了方向的人
Someone who didn't know where they were going...
并且彻底不见了  就像...
And moved radically, as if lost or...
柯顿  你搞什么鬼
Cotton! What in the hell?
不是鬼  小约翰
Oh, not hell, Johnny,
也不是神
Nor heaven.
是大地
Just earth...
光辉无比的大地
Glorious, glorious earth.
恐怕牧师已经神志不清了
I fear the reverend has gone mad.
柯顿  赶紧给我滚下来
Cotton, get your drunk ass down here.
不  我就不
No, sir, I will not.
我在这儿站得高看得远
I can see far more clearly from here.
不光看得远  什么都看得见
In fact, I can see everything.
我看到上帝正亲身走过这片树林
God himself walks among these woods,
身后流动着五彩祥云
Trailing clouds of animal glory.
你到底怎么了
What happened to you?
我把靴子拖了
I took my boots off.
然后呢
Yeah, so?
然后我就感觉到了大地
So, I felt the earth!
在我赤裸的双脚下
I felt the raw,
我感觉到了这原始的  神圣的土地
sacred earth beneath my naked feet.
我感觉到了大地的呼吸
I felt the earth breathe.
赶紧回家
Go home.
要是你那强大的感知力是真的
If your great insight is real,
那回你屋里也一样能继续感知
It will be just as real in your chambers
而且安全得多
And a whole lot safer.
森林的空气
The forest air and this...
和这挺拔的大树  现在是我的老师了
Sturdy tree are my teachers now.
咱们没时间跟他耗着了
We haven't time for this.
我还有很多要学的呢
I still have much to learn!
你到底什么时候把灵魂出卖给魔鬼的
When exactly did you sell your soul to the devil?
我的身体已经被买卖过很多次了
My body was bought and sold many times,
但我从未出卖过灵魂
But never my soul,
直到我来了塞勒姆
Not until I came to salem.
年幼的我被关在笼子里
I am a child in a cage,
在船上得到的食物比畜生还少
Given less to eat than the animals on the ship.
我很怕自己再也无法重见天日了
I fear I will never see the sun again.
然后  来了一个男人
And then a man comes.
就是他把我带到了塞勒姆
It was he that brought me to Salem,
他买我只是为了再把我卖出去
Only to be bought and sold again.
我被一次又一次转卖
I am sold from hand to hand, from man to man.
但起码我不用再待在笼子里了
But at least I am no longer in a cage.
而且最后买下我的还是个好人家
And my final owner is not cruel.
沃科特家给了我一张可以睡觉的床
The Wolcotts give me a bed to sleep in.
他们家的女儿  玛丽  待我亲如姐妹
Their girl child, Mary, treats me almost like a sister.
但每到夜晚  我仍会为了母亲而哭泣
But still at night, I weep for my mother,
我哭着从自己的草榻上跑出去
And I ride a river of tears out of my straw bed,
跑进了黑森林
Into the dark woods.
黑森林
The dark woods?
你去黑森林见谁
Who do you meet in the dark woods?
卡耐马恶鬼
The kenaima.
他是来救我的  来救我们所有人
He has come to save me... save all of us.
他召唤所有受伤的人们
He draws to him all who hurt,
所有在躲藏的人们
All who hide,
所有心怀仇恨的人们
All who hate,
所有渴望正义的人们
All who thirst for justice,
他将我们召集成一圈
Gathers us into the circle
许诺给我们一个领袖
and promises us a leader,
一个救世主
A savior,
一个将用神力击溃敌人的人
One who will crush our enemies with a mighty fist.
他是个信守承诺的人
And he keeps his promise.
姑娘
Girl,
我也是个信守承诺的人
I, too, keep my promises.
我现在许诺你
And I promise you now
如果你不告诉我那圈子里还有谁
I will put your eyes out this instant
我就立马把你的眼珠子挖出来
If you do not tell me who is in the circle,
都有谁  说名字
Who, the names,
巫师的圈子里还有谁
Who is in the circle of witches.
告诉我
Tell me.
真是坚强啊
What fortitude.
因无情的压迫而团结一致
Solidarity amongst the rudely oppressed.
相互鼓舞
Inspiring.It's...
真是太感人了
it's all so very touching.
但我要告诉你  你上当了
But I tell you, you're duped.
这些东西可不是你的朋友
These creatures are not your friends,
他们不是任何人的朋友
Nor anyone's friends.
他们是所有人类的敌人
They are the enemies of all mankind.
告诉我  到底是谁挑起了
Tell me, who started this war
这场巫师和清教徒的战争
Between witches and puritans,
是四处分散的他们  还是人多势众的你们
The scattered few of them or the mighty many of you?
就按你说的来理解
By your own admission,
这些东西为了复仇
These creatures have sold their very souls
将灵魂出卖给了魔鬼
For vengeance to the devil.
不是吗
Is this not so?
你们的人就没当过奴隶吗
Were your people never slaves?
他们从未在荒野中哭喊着寻求正义吗
Did they never cry out in the wilderness for justice?
你们的上帝听到他们的哭喊
And did your god not hear their cries
难道不是报以雷击吗
and answer with thunder?
你还不明白吗
Don't you see?
根本没有巫师
There are no witches,
只有像我这样的可怜人
Only poor people like me,
被围追堵截
hunted and harried,
折磨灭口
tortured and murdered,
没什么别的理由 只因为他们不是你
and for no reason other than they are not you!
她来过这儿
She was here.
我又找到她的痕迹了
I've got her track again.
不管发生什么
No matter what happens,
保持冷静别说话
just stay calm and say nothing.
[土人语]
你真是谜中之谜  上尉
You are a mystery within a mystery, captain.
像猎食者般在丛林游走
Walk the woods like a predator,
如同自己也是土人一样和他们顺畅交流
speak to savages as if you were one of them.
他们看见她了  但没有动她
They saw her, but they did not touch her.
你相信他们吗
And you believe them?
我信
I do.
他们用了一个词来形容她
They used a word to describe her.
这词有很多意思
It can mean a lot of different things,
不过一般它是指"疯狂"
but it usually just means "Crazy."
有很多词可以形容我女儿  上尉
My daughter is many things, captain,
但是疯狂绝不是其中之一
but crazy is not one of them.
他们这么认为真是她走运
Well, lucky for her they thought she was.
他们觉得疯子是我们称之为圣人的人
They think crazy people are what we call holy...
世界与世界间的游走者
Walkers between worlds.
你能想到什么吗
Make any sense to you?
你问我谁挑起的战争
You ask me who began this war.
作为一个
As one scarred
抗争了40年的老兵
with 40 years soldiering in it,
我现在告诉你
I tell you now...
这根本不重要
It does not matter...
只有战争结束才重要
...only that it end.
战争会结束
And end it will.
你等族类希望渺茫
You and your kind have no hope.
你们会流血  会受伤
You will bleed, and you will hurt...
最后在绝望中死去
and you will die in a hopeless cause.
爱不会让人绝望
Love is not a hopeless cause.
我是不会背叛我此生真爱的
I will not betray the one true love of my life.
我懂了
I understand.
我终于懂了
Finally I understand it all.
什么都懂了
I understand everything.
可怜的家伙
You poor thing.
就是个小女孩
Just a little girl,
被绑架  奴役  孤独一人
kidnapped, enslaved, alone,
寻求世人的理解
seeking understanding,
和安慰
comfort...
寻求爱
seeking love.
你还不明白吗
Do you not see?
我不怀疑你爱着
I do not doubt that you love.
但现在你和我单独在这里  诚实点吧
But just for this one moment here alone with me, be honest,
不是对我  至少也对你自己
if not with me, at least with yourself.
你真的相信他们像你爱着他们
Do you really believe that they love you
那样地爱你吗
as much as you love them?
想想吧  女人
Think, woman.
想想他  那个人
Think of that, that person.
在脑海里描绘他们
Picture them in your mind.
你了解他们
You know them so well.
考虑一下他们是什么人
Consider who they are,
不是你希望他们是什么人  而是他们的真面目
not who you wish them to be, but who they really are,
扪心自问  要是躺在这儿的是他们
and ask yourself, were they here,
到底会不会供出你的名字
would they or would they not offer up your name
以求自保
to save themselves?
他们会瞬间背叛你来保全自身
They would betray you in an instant to save themselves,
这就是你爱的人
and this is the person that you love
绝不会像你爱他那样地爱你
and who will never love you the same way.
真的值得吗  你忍受的恐惧
Is it worth it all, the horrors you have endured,
和煎熬
and the agonies...
还有你面前那无比丑陋的死亡
...and the ugly, ugly death you have in front of you?
这是你真心想要的吗
Is that really what you want,
在你已经对自己敞开心扉
now that you have now admitted to yourself
看清了他们的真面目之后
who they really are?
缇图芭
Tituba...
你知道世间最大的欢愉是什么吗
Do you know the greatest pleasure in the world?
就是当痛苦停止的时刻
It is when the pain stops.
痛苦会停止的
And stop it will.
你只要告诉我一个名字
You have but to tell me a name.
轻轻说出来就好
Just whisper it.
告诉我谁是塞勒姆
Tell me who is the leader
巫师中的领头人
of the witches in Salem.
我发誓  你要找的人...
On my soul, the one you seek...
还能更糟吗
It could be worse.
竟然下雨了
It could be raining.
你终于找到回家的路了
At last, you found your way home.
安
Anne!
没事了
It's all right.
我以为我失去你了
I thought I'd lost you.
我也是
Me too.
怎么找到的
How?
你们怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
多谢奥登上尉吧
Give all credit to captain Alden
他在丛林里那些不可思议的技巧
and his preternatural skills in these woods.
只要找到这里  追踪足迹就很简单了
Following the tracks was easy once I found my way out here.
但我不明白你是怎么离开塞勒姆这么远的
But what I can't figure is how you got so far out of Salem
中间的路途几乎无迹可寻
Leaving so few tracks and traces between here and there.
我傻傻的  还闹着脾气
I am a silly thing, and in a fit of petulance,
我跑进了林子
I-I ran into these woods
根本没思考要去哪  或是天有多晚
without thinking where I was going or how late it was...
等反应过来已经太迟了
Until it was too late.
离开塞勒姆没留下任何踪迹
Without leaving any tracks out of Salem.
在我徘徊的时候
It... it rained briefly while I was...
下了会雨
wandering.
也许洗刷掉了我的踪迹
Perhaps that washed away my tracks,
或者是你没找到
or perhaps you just didn't find them.
不管怎样
In either case...
请原谅我
please forgive me
带给你们两位的麻烦
for the trouble I've put you both through.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我相信如果我有需要
Well, I'm sure you'd do the same thing for me
你也会
if I ever needed...
救我的
Rescuing.
你说得没错
You were correct.
她的确是位非凡的女子
She's a remarkable young woman.
我可以明白她为什么不仅仅
I can understand why she's not merely your...
是你的仆人  还是你的朋友
your servant, but your friend, as well.
我发现了一些非常了不起的事
I've discovered something quite extraordinary.
我发现了很多爱
I find so much love.
爱
Love?
令我不解的是
What I did not understand
塞勒姆的巫师统领
was that the chief witch of Salem
不仅仅是她的领袖
is not merely her leader...
也是她的爱人
but her lover.
她招供了吗
She confessed?
爱是一枚双面硬币  不是吗
Love is a-a two-faced coin, is it not?
有一面必定代表背叛
And one face is surely betrayal.
你介意吗
Do you mind?
什么
What?
请便
Oh. Yes, please.
我不常放纵  但是
I rarely indulge, but...
我感觉需要恢复点元气
I feel the need of a restorative.
乔治啊  乔治
Oh, George George.
他总是能做出殖民地里最好的酒窖
He's always cultivated the finest cellar in the colony,
我刚说什么来的
What was I saying?
爱
Love.
对
Yes.
你知道吗
You know...
虽然事实如此  但没有人会承认
It is true that, and no one will admit,
爱情并不平等
that love is never equal.
而它的不平等
And in its inequality
成就了它的脆弱
lies its fragility,
被爱的更少的那一方
for the one who is loved less
总有一天会觉得爱情如烟
will one day find love tastes like ashes.
这也是缇图芭小姐现在的心情
That is indeed what poor Miss Tituba found.
不过她倒是跟我说了一切
But she did tell me everything,
她先跟我说了梅西·路易丝
And she started with Mercy Lewis.
梅西
Mercy?
梅西·路易丝也许一开始是
Mercy Lewis may well have begun
邪恶的受害者  但是她
as a victim of malice, but she...
她被攻击她的野兽变成了女巫
she was made witch by the very beast that assailed her.
她不在这
She's not here.
她下午出去了
Uh, she went out this afternoon.
她还没回来
She's not returned.
那并不是很重要
Well, it is no great matter.
反正  她还能跑到哪去
After all, where can she run to?
我会在太阳升起前
I will have her and her girls
抓住她和她的那些女孩们
by the time the sun comes up.
我刚回到萨勒姆的时候
When I first returned to Salem,
我曾非常坚信撒旦的同伴
I was convinced that satan's true partner
就在我的眼前
was right in front of me
而我需要做的就是伸出手抓住她
and all I need do is reach out my hand to take her.
你可以想象当我知道约翰·奥登上尉
You can imagine my shock to discover that Captain John Alden
是萨勒姆恐怖事件的幕后黑手时有多惊讶
stands behind all of Salem's horror.
我恐怕  需要呼吸点新鲜空气
I fear I...need a breath of air.
能和我出去走走吗  玛丽·西布里
Will you walk with me, Mary Sibley,
在夜晚的清爽中
In the evening air...
也许我们能找到一个好地方
where we may have a good vantage point
观看一场逮捕
from which to witness an arrest?
我想回去看看柯顿怎么样了
I'm tempted to go back, see if Cotton's all right.
他可能会在森林里迷路
He could get lost in those woods
然后在熊的肚子里醒来
and wake up inside the belly of a bear.
他在那
There he is!
约翰·奥登
John Alden...
奉英克里斯·麦哲之命
...by order of Increase Mather
以塞勒姆行政委员之名
and in the name of the selectmen of Salem,
我宣布逮捕你
I place you under arrest.
这次又是因为什么
What for this time?
公开说脏话吗
Swearing in public?
巫术
Witchcraft.
解除他的武装  拷上他
Disarm him, shackle him.
不
No!
不  父亲  阻止他们
No! Father, stop them!
父亲  求你了
Father, please!
求你了  你有能力  你可以做些什么
Please! You have the power to do something!
等着
Wait.